Finding Aid for School of Social Work (University of Michigan) Publications 1935-[ongoing]
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Sub-Unit Publications
  - Mental Health Community Intervention Program
    - Handbooks
      - A Handbook for Community Mental Health and Family Service Professionals, 1975 (Box 3)
  - National Assessment of Juvenile Corrections
    - Reports
      - Juvenile Corrections in the States: Residential Programs and Deinstitutionalization, A Preliminary Report by Robert A. Vinter et al, 1975 (Box 3)
      - Time Out: A National Study of Juvenile Correctional Programs edited by Robert D. Vinter, 1976 (Box 3)
  - National Child Welfare Training Center
    - Bibliographies
      - Sources: Resources for Education and Training in Child Welfare, no. 4, 1984 (Box 3)
    - Handbooks
      - Black Adoption Programs: Pacesetters in Practice, 1984 (Box 3)
    - Newsletters
      - Notes from the National Center, 1980-1981 (Box 3)
    - Proceedings
      - Empowering the Black Family: A Roundtable Discussion with Ann Hartman, James Leigh, Jacquelynn Moffett, Elaine Pinderhughes, Barbara Solomon, and Carol Stack, 1985 (Box 3)
  - Office of Continuing Professional Education
    - Schedules
      - Seminar Schedule, 2001-2002 (Box 3)
  - Planning
    - Strategic Plan, 1990 (Box 3)
  - Program for Continuing Education in the Human Services
    - Schedules
      - Spring-Summer Symposium, 1974 (Box 3)
  - Social Work Administration
    - Social Welfare Administration: Curriculum Documents, 1969 (Box 3)
  - Social Work Progress Institute
    - Proceedings
      - Proceedings, 1957 (Box 3)
    - Programs 1953-1958 (Box 3)
- Student Organization Publications
  The Student Publications series contains publications created by student organizations within the School of Social Work. These include newsletters published by the Social Work Student Union under various titles such as The Social Work Student Union Newsletter issued from 1967 to 1969, The Union Newsletter published during 1970/1971, The Newsletter circulated from 1971 to 1972, The Union Stew disseminated in 1974, and Focus printed from 1975 to 1978 and 1981 to 1987.
  - Social Work Students Union
    - Newsletters
      - Focus
        - 1975-1978, 2 folders (Box 3)
        - 1981-1983 (Box 3)
        - 1984-1987 (Box 3)
      - The Newsletter
        - 1971-1972 (Box 3)
      - The Social Work Student Union Newsletter
        - 1967-1969, 2 folders (Box 3)
      - The Union Newsletter
        - 1970-1971 (Box 3)
      - The Union Stew
        - 1974 (Box 3)
- Archived School of Social Work Website
  The Archived Website series documents the academic programs, accomplishments, resources, events, and people at the School of Social Work. Content includes important news and announcements, publications (such as newsletters and course catalogs), and information about admissions, curriculum, degree requirements, faculty, and the overall mission of the School. The website series is arranged chronologically, with captures from 2002 and 2003 stored on CD. Starting in 2010, this archived website will be captured on a regular, ongoing basis as part of the University of Michigan Web Archives, hosted at http://webarchives.cdlib.org/a/universityofmichigan/.
  - Website capture May 15, 2002, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 2)
    (Original URL http://www.ssw.umich.edu)
  - Website capture May 22, 2003, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 3)
  - Archived School of Social Work home page, 2010-[ongoing]
  - Archived websites related to the School of Social Work, 2010-[ongoing]